The violence of the war between the two civilisations
was such it could have split the world in two.
From this unending war,
the Iron Giant was to be the ultimate weapon,
created to bring absolute victory.
However, through his unlimited and uncontrollable power,
he would soon become the world’s new tyrant.
The Iron Giant devastated the world,
and the rare survivors fled aboard airships,
awaiting an opportunity to put an end to his path of destruction.
At the night of the third day,
taking advantage of a moment of lethargy,
the survivors snatched five crucial pieces from his heart –
and that is how they managed to neutralise him.
Aah… So…
What the Black Cats are trying to do is…
– Yay!
– Can you hear me, Waffle?
Surrender yourself and hand over the crystals!
Alicia…
There is no way I’m
giving you these crystals!